Kamlesh Pandey

kpandey@ncsu.edu | +1 (984) 810-9759 | Raleigh, 27606 | LinkedIn | Website

SUMMARY

Master student at North Carolina State University, planning to concentrate on optimization modeling and data science. Skilled in Python, TensorFlow, R with work experience of six years as Supply chain planner and optimization analyst.

Actively looking for Summer 2022 internships.

EDUCATION

Master of Science, Industrial Engineering North Carolina State University, Raleigh

Aug 2021 – May 2023 GPA-3.11/4.0

Bachelor of Technology, Mechanical Engineer Dehradun Institute of Technology, Dehradun

Aug 2011 - May 2015 Percentage:75.5/100

EXPERIENCE

Supply Chain Optimization Analyst, NewAge Product Inc. Mumbai,

Feb 2021-Aug 2021

- Optimized container loading plans using Cubmaster solver to maximize space utilization, saved an average of two 40" high cube containers per month
- Identification and prioritization of inbound shipment related issues at 13 distribution centers across the USA and Canada
- Achieved more than 90% of accuracy in the Item Master Data/ Product specification database of non-garage SKUs
- Monitored inventory level at 13 distribution centers and flagged overstock, out-of-stock and slow-moving inventory
- Inventory audit of non-garage SKUs at each warehouse level

Supply Chain Planning Manager, Reliance Industries Ltd. Mumbai

June 2015 - Feb 2021

- Served as a logistic planner & scheduler of oil tanker loads across RIL's rail and coastal terminals with daily product sale of 190 TKL
- Over 90% database accuracy of five oil marketing companies' customer master database
- Configured Trading/dispatch location units including vendor creation, product configuration, and plant creation, currently strategically located 44 locations pan India
- Provided Master Data Management (MDM), Inventory Management, and material requirement planning services to five government and private companies
- Averaged 70 rail rakes/ 180 TKL product movement from Jamnagar refinery to three hinterland rail terminals
- Delivered purchase requisition orders for 44 active dispatch units fortnightly basis using SAP MM module, average 90-100 TKL purchase per month

PROJECT

Terminal SAP Integration

~RIL'2017

Integration of oil tanker loading process from rail and coastal terminals with SAP, provided interactive web-based portal for indent creation, tracking and, scheduling, led to cycle time reduction by average $30 \, \text{min}$

• Vessel Scheduling Model with Profit Point (Aspen Technology Partner)

~RIL'2018

Worked with Analytical Team of Profit Point for coastal scheduling model for an optimized loading plan of 90 to 120 forward days

• Rail Planning & Scheduling Model (Excel, What's Best Solver)

~RIL'2018

Scheduling model for product movement via rakes, generating wagon and location combinations as decision variables after meeting all loading constraints

• Reliance BP Mobility Ltd. Company Configuration

~RIL^2020

Created customer master database of 1400+ retail outlets of RBML, (RIL & British Petroleum join venture) in RIL's SAP system

Leaf Disease Classification Using TensorFlow

~Fall'2

Machine learning model using TF & Keras to predict disease class using pretrained neural network model Efficient Net

SKILL

Program Language: Excel Python | TensorFlow | Pandas | NumPy | Julia | Matplotlib

Professional: Supply Chain Planning | Optimization | Scheduling | SAP | Demand Planning | Purchase & Sales